<apartments>
<apartment>
<name>Prestigue Apartments</name>
<address>+256-717-820100, +256-717-820100, +256-772-820100
Prestige Apartments P.O. Box 6219 Kampala Uganda</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>We aim to offer you the highest quality accommodation available in Kampala,
 Uganda at a price that reflects the best value for your money. And are committed to ensure
 that you have a pleasant stay with us and therefore focus on the quality of service, right 
 from the instance you make an enquiry.</description>
<image>prestigue</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Uganda Property Promotions</name>
<address>Plot 33, Nkurumah Road
Kampala, Uganda, +256 782 732572, info@propertypromotions.co.ug</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>The company has its core business in the city centre; we provide a great source
 of information to the up market, urban clientele, the Ugandans living in the Diaspora and 
 foreigners (expatriates or tourists) moving into country for short or long stay.</description>
<image>property</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Haven Apartments</name>
<address>Plot 25 Bazeketta Road, Rubaga, nextnext to Uganda Martyrs’ High School Rubaga 
(jrtn to playground)P. O. Box 23086 Kampala, Uganda, +256-75-2644-366, +256-77-2407119, 
+256-75-2695-259 Cell: +256-71-255-9546, reservations@thehavenapartments.biz OR 
thehavenapartments@yahoo.com</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>Welcome to The Haven Apartments Kampala Uganda. Kampala's unique boutique 
apartments.Gracious and elegant, The Haven Apartments ensures a happy stay for today's 
business and leisure traveller requires. </description>
<image>haven</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Posh Properties Limited</name>
<address>0703 995674, 
bukenyaisa@yahoo.com</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description></description>
<image></image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>National Housing</name>
<address>P.O Box 659,Plot 5, 7th Street, Industrial Area, Kampala 256, Uganda, 0414-330002,
0414-258708</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>National Housing and Construction Company Ltd is a private limited company registered 
under the Companies Act. The Company’s mandate is to increase the housing stock in the country, 
rehabilitate the housing industry and encourage Ugandans to own homes in an organized environment.
</description>
<image>housing</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Guide 2 Uganda</name>
<address>Tel: +256 (0) 312 515 167 / +256 (0) 774 795 432
info@guide2uganda.com, 112 New Port Bell Road, Akamwesi Complex Nakawa,
P.O Box 10287,Kampala, Uganda</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>Guide2Uganda aims to be the complete source of information for Uganda. Designed especially for those who 
are planning a holiday in Uganda, contemplating buying property in Uganda or residents of Uganda, Guide2Uganda provides 
Property and Accommodation listings, Uganda News, Events in Uganda, Town information as well as Classified listings, 
a Business Directory and Blog</description>
<image>logo</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Gabe International Homes</name>
<address>Plot 1001 Ggaba Road (Next to the American Embassy).
Suzie House, Annex. 1st Floor, Kampala, Uganda, +256791525600, +256701525600, sales@propertyuganda.com</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>With Property Uganda, you are bound to see a vast selection of the properties and commercial premises 
available to your disposal. Our offices are located at a close proximity from the U. S. A (United States of America) 
Embassy.</description>
<image></image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Mowin</name>
<address>PLOT 3 PARLIAMENT AVENUE, RAJA CHAMBERS(OPPOSITE FORMER BRITISH HIGH COMMISSION),2ND FLOOR ROOM 36,
P.O. BOX: 4801, KAMPALA, UGANDA, 041-4-235795 (OFFICE), 077-2-439777, 071-2-815-022, 070-2-439777 
mowinproperties@gmail.com, mowinproperties@gmail.com </address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>We are based in the city centre Kampala, the capital of Uganda which has approximately one million inhabitants. 
This city takes its name from kasozi k'mpala "the hill of the antelopes" and its origins go back to 1891 when the kabaka 
(king of Buganda) had his court on Rubaga and Mengo hills (one of the hills that now make up Kampala</description>
<image>mowin</image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Ugandan Hotels</name>
<address>+256 777 887 947, P.O BOX 29132, info@ugandanhotels.com</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>Uganda Apartments, an alternative accommodation option for tourists and holiday makers in Uganda available for
rent on daily or monthly basis.Accommodationinuganda.com provides discount options for traveller for both Short and long stays.
Book your apartment in Uganda with us and enjoy the best and affordable apartment rates.</description>
<image></image>
</apartment>

<apartment>
<name>Online Real Estate Uganda</name>
<address>Plot 53 Kiira Road Kamwokya Kampala, Uganda, Tel: +256 772 483  978, +256 701 976 983
info@onlinerealestate.co.ug</address>
<district>Kampala</district>
<description>Welcome to Uganda Property. Works in partnership with local registered agencies to provide 
up to date, definitive information regarding available properties and land for purchase or rent 
throughout Uganda.</description>
<image>housebox150</image>
</apartment>

</apartments>